<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">COVID PROTECTOR</string>
    <string name="main_image">sanitizer,gloves andhandwash image</string>
    <string name="main_image_home">sanitizer,gloves and handwash image</string>
    <string name="wear_mask">2.Wear Mask</string>
    <string name="wear_a_mask_in_public_especially_indoors_when_physical_distancing_is_not_possible">Wear a mask in public, especially indoors when physical distancing is not possible.</string>
    <string name="description">an image</string>
    <string name="social_distancing">1.Social Distancing</string>
    <string name="maintain_a_safe_distance_from_others_at_least_2_metre_or_6_feet_even_if_they_don_t_appear_to_be_sick">Maintain a safe distance from others (at least 2 metre or 6 feet), even if they don\'t appear to be sick.</string>
    <string name="next"><![CDATA[NEXT>]]></string>
    <string name="stay_home">6.Stay Home</string>
    <string name="stay_home_if_you_feel_unwell">Stay home if you feel unwell.</string>
    <string name="go_back_home">GO BACK HOME</string>
    <string name="wash_your_hands">3.Wash Your Hands</string>
    <string name="clean_your_hands_often_use_soap_and_water_or_an_alcohol_based_hand_rub_or_sanitizer">Clean your hands often. Use soap and water, or an alcohol-based hand rub, or sanitizer.</string>
    <string name="get_vaccinated">4.Get vaccinated</string>
    <string name="get_vaccinated_when_it_s_your_turn_follow_local_guidance_about_vaccination">Get vaccinated when it\'s your turn. Follow local guidance about vaccination.</string>
    <string name="how_to_sneeze">5.How To Sneeze</string>
    <string name="cover_your_nose_and_mouth_with_your_bent_elbow_or_a_tissue_when_you_cough_or_sneeze">Cover your nose and mouth with your bent elbow or a tissue when you cough or sneeze.</string>
    <string name="carry_cleaners">1.Carry Cleaners</string>
    <string name="carry_cleaners_antiviral_wipes_alcohol_pads_hand_sanitizer_if_you_can_find_some_keep_them_in_your_car_so_you_have_them_handy_and_carry_them_around_when_you_go_out">CARRY CLEANERS // Antiviral wipes // Alcohol pads // Hand sanitizer //(if you can find //some) //Keep them in your car so you //have them handy, and carry //them around when you go out.</string>
    <string name="lather_up">2.Lather Up!</string>
    <string name="wash_your_hands_for_at_least_20_seconds_with_soap_and_water_especially_after_using_the_restroom">Wash your hands for at least //20 seconds with soap and water, //especially after using //the restroom.</string>
    <string name="stand_tall">3.Stand Tall</string>
    <string name="avoid_leaning_against_walls_counters_and_railings_do_not_sit_on_floors_or_steps">Avoid leaning against walls, counters, and railings. Do not sit on floors or steps.</string>
    <string name="hand_awareness">4.Hand Awareness</string>
    <string name="limit_the_number_of_surfaces_you_touch_especially_when_you_are_in_public_place">Limit the number of surfaces you touch especially when you are in public place.</string>
    <string name="face_off">5.Face Off!</string>
    <string name="we_know_it_s_tough_but_keep_your_hands_off_your_face_eyes_mouth_and_hair">We know it’s tough— but keep your hands off your face, eyes, mouth, and hair.</string>
    <string name="keep_everything_clean">6.Keep Everything Clean</string>
    <string name="especially_all_high_touch_surfaces_in_your_home_and_car_also_be_sure_to_clean_your_hands_before_and_after_entering_your_home_and_car">Especially all high-touch surfaces in your home and car. Also, be sure to clean your hands before and after entering your home and car.</string>
    <string name="check_your_mask">7.Check Your Mask</string>
    <string name="check">CHECK</string>
    <string name="to_check_that_you_have_weared_mask_properly_make_sure_your_mouth_and_nose_are_coverd_click_on_check_button_to_open_camera_and_check">Check that you have wear mask properly.Make sure your mouth and nose are cover.</string>
    <string name="antiviral_wipes_alcohol_pads_and_hand_sanitizer_if_you_can_find_some_keep_them_in_your_car_so_you_have_them_handy_and_carry_them_around_when_you_go_out">Antiviral wipes, Alcohol pads and Hand sanitizer (if you can find some) Keep them in your car so you have them handy, and carry them around when you go out.</string>
    <string name="wash_your_hands_for_at_least_20_seconds_with_soap_and_water_especially_after_using_the_restroom_">Wash your hands for at least 20 seconds with soap and water, especially after using the restroom.</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="status">Status:</string>
    <string name="covid_protector">COVID PROTECTOR</string>
    <string name="what_is_corona_virus">What is corona virus?</string>
    <string name="corona_viruses_are_a_large_family_of_viruses_which_may_cause_illness_in_animals_or_humans_in_humans_several_coronaviruses_are_known_to_cause_respiratory_infections_ranging_from_the_common_cold_to_more_severe_diseases_such_as_middle_east_respiratory_syndrome_mers_and_severe_acute_respiratory_syndrome_sars_the_most_recently_discovered_coronavirus_causes_coronavirus_disease_covid_19">Corona viruses are a large family of viruses which may cause illness in animals or humans. In humans, several coronaviruses are known to cause respiratory infections ranging from the common cold to more severe diseases such as Middle East Respiratory Syndrome (MERS) and Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS). The most recently discovered coronavirus causes coronavirus disease COVID-19.</string>
    <string name="covid_19_is_the_infectious_disease_caused_by_the_most_recently_discovered_corona_virus_this_new_virus_and_disease_were_unknown_before_the_outbreak_began_in_wuhan_china_in_december_2019">COVID-19 is the infectious disease caused by the most recently discovered corona virus. This new virus and disease were unknown before the outbreak began in Wuhan, China, in December 2019.</string>
    <string name="what_is_covid_19">What is COVID-19?</string>
    <string name="people_can_catch_covid_19_from_others_who_have_the_virus_the_disease_can_spread_from_person_to_person_through_small_droplets_from_the_nose_or_mouth_which_are_spread_when_a_person_with_covid_19_coughs_or_exhales_these_droplets_land_on_objects_and_surfaces_around_the_person_other_people_then_catch_covid_19_by_touching_these_objects_or_surfaces_then_touching_their_eyes_nose_or_mouth_people_can_also_catch_covid_19_if_they_breathe_in_droplets_from_a_person_with_covid_19_who_coughs_out_or_exhales_droplets_this_is_why_it_is_important_to_stay_more_than_1_meter_3_feet_away_from_a_person_who_is_sick">People can catch COVID-19 from others who have the virus. The disease can spread from person to person through small droplets from the nose or mouth which are spread when a person with COVID-19 coughs or exhales. These droplets land on objects and surfaces around the person. Other people then catch COVID-19 by touching these objects or surfaces, then touching their eyes, nose or mouth. People can also catch COVID-19 if they breathe in droplets from a person with COVID-19 who coughs out or exhales droplets. This is why it is important to stay more than 1 meter (3 feet) away from a person who is sick.</string>
    <string name="how_does_covid_19_spread">How does COVID-19 spread?</string>
    <string name="studies_to_date_suggest_that_the_virus_that_causes_covid_19_is_mainly_transmitted_through_contact_with_respiratory_droplets_rather_than_through_the_air">Studies to date suggest that the virus that causes COVID-19 is mainly transmitted through contact with respiratory droplets rather than through the air.</string>
    <string name="can_the_virus_that_causes_covid_19_be_transmitted_through_the_air">Can the virus that causes COVID-19 be transmitted through the air?</string>
    <string name="can_covid_19_be_caught_from_a_person_who_has_no_symptoms">Can CoVID-19 be caught from a person who has no symptoms?</string>
    <string name="can_i_catch_covid_19_from_the_feces_of_someone_with_the_disease">Can I catch COVID-19 from the feces of someone with the disease?</string>
    <string name="the_risk_of_catching_covid_19_from_the_feces_of_an_infected_person_appears_to_be_low_while_initial_investigations_suggest_the_virus_may_be_present_in_feces_in_some_cases_spread_through_this_route_is_not_a_main_feature_of_the_outbreak_the_ongoing_research_on_the_ways_covid_19_is_spread_and_will_continue_to_share_new_findings_because_this_is_a_risk_however_it_is_another_reason_to_clean_hands_regularly_after_using_the_bathroom_and_before_eating">The risk of catching COVID-19 from the feces of an infected person appears to be low. While initial investigations suggest the virus may be present in feces in some cases, spread through this route is not a main feature of the outbreak. The ongoing research on the ways COVID-19 is spread and will continue to share new findings. Because this is a risk, however, it is another reason to clean hands regularly, after using the bathroom and before eating.</string>
    <string name="how_likely_am_i_to_catch_covid_19">How likely am I to catch COVID-19?</string>
    <string name="the_risk_depends_on_where_you_are_and_more_specifically_whether_there_is_a_covid_19_outbreak_unfolding_there_for_most_people_in_most_locations_the_risk_of_catching_covid_19_is_still_low_however_there_are_now_places_around_the_world_cities_or_areas_where_the_disease_is_spreading_for_people_living_in_or_visiting_these_areas_the_risk_of_catching_covid_19_is_higher_governments_and_health_authorities_are_taking_vigorous_action_every_time_a_new_case_of_covid_19_is_identified_be_sure_to_comply_with_any_local_restrictions_on_travel_movement_or_large_gatherings_cooperating_with_disease_control_efforts_will_reduce_your_risk_of_catching_or_spreading_covid_19_covid_19_outbreaks_can_be_contained_and_transmission_stopped_as_has_been_shown_in_china_and_some_other_countries_unfortunately_new_outbreaks_can_emerge_rapidly_it_s_important_to_be_aware_of_the_situation_where_you_are_or_intend_to_go">The risk depends on where you are - and more specifically, whether there is a COVID-19 outbreak unfolding there. For most people in most locations the risk of catching COVID-19 is still low. However, there are now places around the world (cities or areas) where the disease is spreading. For people living in, or visiting, these areas the risk of catching COVID-19 is higher. Governments and health authorities are taking vigorous action every time a new case of COVID-19 is identified. Be sure to comply with any local restrictions on travel, movement or large gatherings. Cooperating with disease control efforts will reduce your risk of catching or spreading COVID-19. COVID-19 outbreaks can be contained and transmission stopped, as has been shown in China and some other countries. Unfortunately, new outbreaks can emerge rapidly. It’s important to be aware of the situation where you are or intend to go.</string>
    <string name="should_i_worry_about_covid_19">Should I worry about COVID-19?</string>
    <string name="illness_due_to_covid_19_infection_is_generally_mild_especially_for_children_and_young_adults_however_it_can_cause_serious_illness_about_1_in_every_5_people_who_catch_it_need_hospital_care_it_is_therefore_quite_normal_for_people_to_worry_about_how_the_covid_19_outbreak_will_affect_them_and_their_loved_ones_we_can_channel_our_concerns_into_actions_to_protect_ourselves_our_loved_ones_and_our_communities_first_and_foremost_among_these_actions_is_regular_and_thorough_hand_washing_and_good_respiratory_hygiene_secondly_keep_informed_and_follow_the_advice_of_the_local_health_authorities_including_any_restrictions_put_in_place_on_travel_movement_and_gatherings">Illness due to COVID-19 infection is generally mild, especially for children and young adults. However, it can cause serious illness: about 1 in every 5 people who catch it need hospital care. It is therefore quite normal for people to worry about how the COVID-19 outbreak will affect them and their loved ones. We can channel our concerns into actions to protect ourselves, our loved ones and our communities. First and foremost among these actions is regular and thorough hand-washing and good respiratory hygiene. Secondly, keep informed and follow the advice of the local health authorities including any restrictions put in place on travel, movement and gatherings.</string>
    <string name="are_antibiotics_effective_in_preventing_or_treating_the_covid_19">Are antibiotics effective in preventing or treating the COVID-19?</string>
    <string name="no_antibiotics_do_not_work_against_viruses_they_only_work_on_bacterial_infections_covid_19_is_caused_by_a_virus_so_antibiotics_do_not_work_antibiotics_should_not_be_used_as_a_means_of_prevention_or_treatment_of_covid_19_they_should_only_be_used_as_directed_by_a_physician_to_treat_a_bacterial_infection">No. Antibiotics do not work against viruses, they only work on bacterial infections. COVID-19 is caused by a virus, so antibiotics do not work. Antibiotics should not be used as a means of prevention or treatment of COVID-19. They should only be used as directed by a physician to treat a bacterial infection.</string>
    <string name="can_i_catch_covid_19_from_my_pet">Can I catch COVID-19 from my pet?</string>
    <string name="while_there_has_been_one_instance_of_a_dog_being_infected_in_hong_kong_to_date_there_is_no_evidence_that_a_dog_cat_or_any_pet_can_transmit_covid_19_covid_19_is_mainly_spread_through_droplets_produced_when_an_infected_person_coughs_sneezes_or_speaks_to_protect_yourself_clean_your_hands_frequently_and_thoroughly_we_continues_to_monitor_the_latest_research_on_this_and_other_covid19_topics_and_will_update_as_new_findings_are_available">While there has been one instance of a dog being infected in Hong Kong, to date, there is no evidence that a dog, cat or any pet can transmit COVID-19. COVID-19 is mainly spread through droplets produced when an infected person coughs, sneezes, or speaks. To protect yourself, clean your hands frequently and thoroughly. We continues to monitor the latest research on this and other COVID19 topics and will update as new findings are available.</string>
    <string name="how_long_does_the_virus_survive_on_surfaces">How long does the virus survive on surfaces?</string>
    <string name="it_is_not_certain_how_long_the_virus_that_causes_covid_19_survives_on_surfaces_but_it_seems_to_behave_like_other_corona_viruses_studies_suggest_that_corona_viruses_including_preliminary_information_on_the_covid_19_virus_may_persist_on_surfaces_for_a_few_hours_or_up_to_several_days_this_may_vary_under_different_conditions_e_g_type_of_surface_temperature_or_humidity_of_the_environment_if_you_think_a_surface_may_be_infected_clean_it_with_simple_disinfectant_to_kill_the_virus_and_protect_yourself_and_others_clean_your_hands_with_an_alcohol_based_hand_rub_or_wash_them_with_soap_and_water_avoid_touching_your_eyes_mouth_or_nose">It is not certain how long the virus that causes COVID-19 survives on surfaces, but it seems to behave like other corona viruses. Studies suggest that corona viruses (including preliminary information on the COVID-19 virus) may persist on surfaces for a few hours or up to several days. This may vary under different conditions (e.g. type of surface, temperature or humidity of the environment). If you think a surface may be infected, clean it with simple disinfectant to kill the virus and protect yourself and others. Clean your hands with an alcohol-based hand rub or wash them with soap and water. Avoid touching your eyes, mouth, or nose.</string>
    <string name="is_it_safe_to_receive_a_package_from_any_area_where_covid_19_has_been_reported">Is it safe to receive a package from any area where COVID-19 has been reported?</string>
    <string name="yes_the_likelihood_of_an_infected_person_contaminating_commercial_goods_is_low_and_the_risk_of_catching_the_virus_that_causes_covid_19_from_a_package_that_has_been_moved_travelled_and_exposed_to_different_conditions_and_temperature_is_also_low">Yes. The likelihood of an infected person contaminating commercial goods is low and the risk of catching the virus that causes COVID-19 from a package that has been moved, travelled, and exposed to different conditions and temperature is also low.</string>
    <string name="who_is_at_risk_of_developing_severe_illness">Who is at risk of developing severe illness</string>
    <string name="while_we_are_still_learning_about_how_covid_2019_affects_people_older_persons_and_persons_with_pre_existing_medical_conditions_such_as_high_blood_pressure_heart_disease_lung_disease_cancer_or_diabetes_appear_to_develop_serious_illness_more_often_than_others">While we are still learning about how COVID-2019 affects people, older persons and persons with pre-existing medical conditions (such as high blood pressure, heart disease, lung disease, cancer or diabetes) appear to develop serious illness more often than others.</string>
    <string name="protection_measures_for_persons_who_are_in_or_have_recently_visited_past_14_days_areas_where_covid_19_is_spreading">Protection measures for persons who are in or have recently visited (past 14 days) areas where COVID-19 is spreading</string>
    <string name="follow_the_guidance_outlined_above_protection_measures_for_everyone_o_self_isolate_by_staying_at_home_if_you_begin_to_feel_unwell_even_with_mild_symptoms_such_as_headache_low_grade_fever_37_3_c_or_above_and_slight_runny_nose_until_you_recover_if_it_is_essential_for_you_to_have_someone_bring_you_supplies_or_to_go_out_e_g_to_buy_food_then_wear_a_mask_to_avoid_infecting_other_people_why_avoiding_contact_with_others_and_visits_to_medical_facilities_will_allow_these_facilities_to_operate_more_effectively_and_help_protect_you_and_others_from_possible_covid_19_and_other_viruses_o_if_you_develop_fever_cough_and_difficulty_breathing_seek_medical_advice_promptly_as_this_may_be_due_to_a_respiratory_infection_or_other_serious_condition_call_in_advance_and_tell_your_provider_of_any_recent_travel_or_contact_with_travelers_why_calling_in_advance_will_allow_your_health_care_provider_to_quickly_direct_you_to_the_right_health_facility_this_will_also_help_to_prevent_possible_spread_of_covid_19_and_other_viruses">Follow the guidance outlined above (Protection measures for everyone) o Self-isolate by staying at home if you begin to feel unwell, even with mild symptoms such as headache, low grade fever (37.3 C or above) and slight runny nose, until you recover. If it is essential for you to have someone bring you supplies or to go out, e.g. to buy food, then wear a mask to avoid infecting other people. Why? Avoiding contact with others and visits to medical facilities will allow these facilities to operate more effectively and help protect you and others from possible COVID-19 and other viruses. o If you develop fever, cough and difficulty breathing, seek medical advice promptly as this may be due to a respiratory infection or other serious condition. Call in advance and tell your provider of any recent travel or contact with travelers. Why? Calling in advance will allow your health care provider to quickly direct you to the right health facility. This will also help to prevent possible spread of COVID-19 and other viruses.</string>
    <string name="the_main_way_the_disease_spreads_is_through_respiratory_droplets_expelled_by_someone_who_is_coughing_the_risk_of_catching_covid_19_from_someone_with_no_symptoms_at_all_is_very_low_however_many_people_with_covid_19_experience_only_mild_symptoms_this_is_particularly_true_at_the_early_stages_of_the_disease_it_is_therefore_possible_to_catch_covid_19_from_someone_who_has_for_example_just_a_mild_cough_and_does_not_feel_ill">The main way the disease spreads is through respiratory droplets expelled by someone who is coughing. The risk of catching COVID-19 from someone with no symptoms at all is very low. However, many people with COVID-19 experience only mild symptoms. This is particularly true at the early stages of the disease. It is therefore possible to catch COVID-19 from someone who has, for example, just a mild cough and does not feel ill.</string>
</resources>